{
    "id": "03cde28b036d4e0eaef40af2925504bc",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The pirate’s ………………….. led him to cheat his partners out of their share.",
            "description": "We need a noun here and greed is a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "greed",
                "magnanimity",
                "greedy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4072901c45ca4dbeb2a825ddc2df6762"
        },
        {
            "question": "She suffered a …………………………. injury.",
            "description": "Injury is a noun and we need an adjective to modify a noun. Grievous is an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "grievous",
                "grief",
                "grievously"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79d1258f238944d0bdfdfd8dd809efe0"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ……………………… insult flabbergasted me.",
            "description": "Gratuitous can mean uncalled for or unwarranted.",
            "answers": [
                "gratuity",
                "gratuitous",
                "gratitude"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "50e4f217b9c0422aa8c3d748dcdb6f2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The situation has reached a point of extreme ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gratuity",
                "gravity",
                "gratitude"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "96e22d1fd8d7447694f32b64313b668d"
        },
        {
            "question": "High blood pressure can be a result of ……………………………",
            "description": "Gluttony means excessive eating. A glutton is an overeater.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "gluttony",
                "glutton"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e260f5795b124a308b764a11d1d4d9ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "What could have been a nasty situation was handled with great …………………………….",
            "description": "Finesse means discretion.",
            "answers": [
                "finesse",
                "finery",
                "filiality"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b9c558db359c4016b98d1513bbb40bbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was much …………………………. affection in the hug she gave her father.",
            "description": "Filial means befitting one’s child.",
            "answers": [
                "filial",
                "fillial",
                "finery"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c8bcfd5e60414e548a83404fbb7bb2b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "They had a lavish ……………………… at their country house.",
            "description": "Fete means grand party.",
            "answers": [
                "feet",
                "feat",
                "fete"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "33cf2c0f80274a379cf9f16cd95abd96"
        },
        {
            "question": "The lawyer made a ………………………. plea for clemency.",
            "description": "Fervent means heartfelt.",
            "answers": [
                "fervent",
                "ferment",
                "foment"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ef9aa8506d249b2b19f4bfa412ae618"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was a tough minded executive but she never lost her ………………………..",
            "description": "Femininity means female quality.",
            "answers": [
                "femine",
                "feminity",
                "femininity"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f3d1ab2319ce4b2496a84407714ba79e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Being locked in a candy store was the boy’s idea of ……………………..",
            "description": "Felicity means happiness or bliss.",
            "answers": [
                "facility",
                "felicity",
                "fecility"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "118fa01ed58b403a808ad16c2e22f5b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is not ………………………… to make the trip in one day.",
            "description": "All of these words mean the same. ",
            "answers": [
                "feasible",
                "possible",
                "practicable",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "884993c1db2f4958904f132cd9df8482"
        }
    ]
}